{
    "userid": 1,
    "username": "admin",
    "email": "user@example.com",
    "signUpDate": "2024-01-13",
    "role": "Admin",
    "stacks": [
        {
            "stackid": 1,
            "name": "Stack 0",
            "userid": 1,
            "cards": [
                {
                    "cardid": 1,
                    "question": "Question 0",
                    "answer": "Answer 0",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-11-10",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 0,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 2,
                    "question": "Question 1",
                    "answer": "Answer 1",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-02-07",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 7,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 3,
                    "question": "Question 2",
                    "answer": "Answer 2",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-03-20",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 8,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 4,
                    "question": "Question 3",
                    "answer": "Answer 3",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-12-22",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 7,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 5,
                    "question": "Question 4",
                    "answer": "Answer 4",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-09-11",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 3,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 6,
                    "question": "Question 5",
                    "answer": "Answer 5",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-09-04",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 5,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 7,
                    "question": "Question 6",
                    "answer": "Answer 6",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-05-17",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 11,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 8,
                    "question": "Question 7",
                    "answer": "Answer 7",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-10-20",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 3,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 9,
                    "question": "Question 8",
                    "answer": "Answer 8",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-11-06",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 4,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 10,
                    "question": "Question 9",
                    "answer": "Answer 9",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-01-26",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 2,
                    "userid": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "stackid": 2,
            "name": "Stack 1",
            "userid": 1,
            "cards": [
                {
                    "cardid": 11,
                    "question": "Question 0",
                    "answer": "Answer 0",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-12-28",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 4,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 12,
                    "question": "Question 1",
                    "answer": "Answer 1",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-04-27",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 5,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 13,
                    "question": "Question 2",
                    "answer": "Answer 2",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-04-08",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 11,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 14,
                    "question": "Question 3",
                    "answer": "Answer 3",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-02-04",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 7,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 15,
                    "question": "Question 4",
                    "answer": "Answer 4",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-06-22",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 1,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 16,
                    "question": "Question 5",
                    "answer": "Answer 5",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-09-20",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 3,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 17,
                    "question": "Question 6",
                    "answer": "Answer 6",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-02-17",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 9,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 18,
                    "question": "Question 7",
                    "answer": "Answer 7",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-05-16",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 4,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 19,
                    "question": "Question 8",
                    "answer": "Answer 8",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-03-30",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 10,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 20,
                    "question": "Question 9",
                    "answer": "Answer 9",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-10-30",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 13,
                    "userid": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "stackid": 3,
            "name": "Stack 2",
            "userid": 1,
            "cards": [
                {
                    "cardid": 21,
                    "question": "Question 0",
                    "answer": "Answer 0",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-02-14",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 12,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 22,
                    "question": "Question 1",
                    "answer": "Answer 1",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-09-28",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 11,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 23,
                    "question": "Question 2",
                    "answer": "Answer 2",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-03-19",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 11,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 24,
                    "question": "Question 3",
                    "answer": "Answer 3",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-09-16",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 13,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 25,
                    "question": "Question 4",
                    "answer": "Answer 4",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-09-17",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 4,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 26,
                    "question": "Question 5",
                    "answer": "Answer 5",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-08-15",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 11,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 27,
                    "question": "Question 6",
                    "answer": "Answer 6",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-10-14",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 0,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 28,
                    "question": "Question 7",
                    "answer": "Answer 7",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-05-07",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 0,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 29,
                    "question": "Question 8",
                    "answer": "Answer 8",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-04-17",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 2,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 30,
                    "question": "Question 9",
                    "answer": "Answer 9",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-10-05",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 15,
                    "userid": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "stackid": 4,
            "name": "Stack 3",
            "userid": 1,
            "cards": [
                {
                    "cardid": 31,
                    "question": "Question 0",
                    "answer": "Answer 0",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-03-16",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 9,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 32,
                    "question": "Question 1",
                    "answer": "Answer 1",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-12-02",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 10,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 33,
                    "question": "Question 2",
                    "answer": "Answer 2",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-06-08",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 12,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 34,
                    "question": "Question 3",
                    "answer": "Answer 3",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-01-06",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 13,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 35,
                    "question": "Question 4",
                    "answer": "Answer 4",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-11-18",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 3,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 36,
                    "question": "Question 5",
                    "answer": "Answer 5",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-11-08",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 12,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 37,
                    "question": "Question 6",
                    "answer": "Answer 6",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2024-07-02",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 13,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 38,
                    "question": "Question 7",
                    "answer": "Answer 7",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-01-31",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 7,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 39,
                    "question": "Question 8",
                    "answer": "Answer 8",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-06-04",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 11,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 40,
                    "question": "Question 9",
                    "answer": "Answer 9",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2025-09-01",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 9,
                    "userid": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "stackid": 5,
            "name": "Stack 4",
            "userid": 1,
            "cards": [
                {
                    "cardid": 41,
                    "question": "Question 0",
                    "answer": "Answer 0",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-06-10",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 8,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 42,
                    "question": "Question 1",
                    "answer": "Answer 1",
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-04-25",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 6,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 43,
                    "question": "Question 2",
                    "answer": "Answer 2",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-11-23",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 9,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 44,
                    "question": "Question 3",
                    "answer": "Answer 3",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-06-12",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 10,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 45,
                    "question": "Question 4",
                    "answer": "Answer 4",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-09-18",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 2,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 46,
                    "question": "Question 5",
                    "answer": "Answer 5",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-03-17",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 2,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 47,
                    "question": "Question 6",
                    "answer": "Answer 6",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-06-21",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 5,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 48,
                    "question": "Question 7",
                    "answer": "Answer 7",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-09-21",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 11,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 49,
                    "question": "Question 8",
                    "answer": "Answer 8",
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-08-25",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 14,
                    "userid": 1
                },
                {
                    "cardid": 50,
                    "question": "Question 9",
                    "answer": "Answer 9",
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "nextReviewDate": "2023-07-01",
                    "timesAnsweredCorrectly": 0,
                    "userid": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}